[{"answer": "Well, if it's as good as", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "\"Ponce de Leo", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm starvin', I haven't had any dinner", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't wanna get a movie hot dog!  I want a Papaya King hot dog", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No! I don't want to save seats. Don't put me through that! I once had the fleece just ripped out of my winter coat in a sea", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, my friend, this is the ticke", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm in line to buy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No it's not, it's the ticke", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend, I want you to do me a favor. No more fish", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I had a point", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "No, I don't have any change", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Or, I could take the twenty, then I could pay", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I mean, how is that easier? I mean, then you would owe me twelve fifty instead of me owing you seven fifty", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "So... Can I have it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Whaddya mean, you'll", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No thanks, maybe some other time", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No, I don't", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " What happened to the small", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What's... medium", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "There is no small. Small is Medium", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Medium is Large, and large is Jumbo", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What's... medium", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "O", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I just went to get popcorn... Ugh...  I just went to get popcorn, okay? And and and somebody took my seat, and my coat is in there", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No no, I can't sit in the front row", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Really..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Weight? Naw. Just need some more height", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Come on, we can still catch most of", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "A young girl's strange, erotic journey from that place to that place", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "\"that plac", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " that place", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Oh, gimme a break", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Movie.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 38}]